Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions PE.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- H, 1910-2006; 3 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America: Local 458 (Northwestern Cooks Association), 1919 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America: Local 484 (Chicago Waitresses), 1921-1926, undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Workers and Bartenders League for Political Education (Cincinnati, OH), undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE), 1980-2000, undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE): Guest Book, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE): Chicago Joint Executive Board, 1983, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE): Local 2 (San Francisco, CA), 1996 (Box 14)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE): Local 100 (New York, NY), undated (Box 14)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE): Local 217 (Granby, CT), undated (Box 14)
- I, 1884-2010; 15 Linear Feet in 14 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 2 oversize shared boxes
  - Icelandic Federation of Labor, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Illinois Mine Workers, undated (Box 14)
  - Independent Association of Publishers, 1990-2002 (Box 14)
  - Independent Association of Publishers' Employees, 1970-1985 (Box 14)
  - Independent Association of Publishers' Employees: Agreements, 1969-1978 (Box 14)
  - Independent Association of Publishers' Employees: Agreements, 1981-2005, undated (Box 14)
  - Independent Association of Publishers' Employees: Contracts, 1957-1996 (Box 14)
  - Independent Bakery Employees Union, 1954 (Box 14)
  - Independent Brotherhood of Truck Drivers and Allied Workers (St. Louis, MO), 1947 (Box 14)
  - Independent Colored Longshoremen's Association of the City of New Orleans and the State of Louisiana, 1934 (Box 14)
  - Independent Federation of Flight Attendants, 1985-1986, undated (Box 14)
  - Independent Owners Taxi Association: Taxi Fleets, undated (Box 14)
  - Independent Railway Benevolent Association, undated (Box 14)
  - Independent Telephone Workers, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Independent Union of Flight Attendants, 1978-1991 (Box 14)
  - Independent Union of Flight Attendants, undated (Box 14)
  - "Independent" Unions, Statistical Analysis of, 1938 (Box 14)
  - Independent Workers of Long Lines, undated (Box 14)
  - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, 1935-1960 (Box 14)
  - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America: Constitutions, 1939-1958 (Box 14)
  - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America: Constitutions, 1962-1980 (Box 14)
  - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America: Leadership Training Program I, undated (Box 14)
  - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America: Leadership Training Program II, undated (Box 14)
  - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America: Training Program I, undated (Box 14)
  - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America: Training Program II, undated (Box 14)
  - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America: Training Program III, undated (Box 14)
  - Industrial Union of Needle Trades Workers of Canada, 1929 (Box 14)
  - Industrial Union of Needle Trades Workers of Canada: Dressmakers' Union. Toronto Joint Council, undated (Box 14)
  - Inland Boatmen's Union of the Pacific, undated (Box 14)
  - Insurance Agents International Union, 1956, undated (Box 14)
  - Insurance Workers International Union, 1960-1979, undated (Box 14)
  - Insurance Workers International Union: Constitutions, 1963-1979 (Box 14)
  - Insurance Workers International Union: Local 5: By-Laws, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Inter-American Confederation of Workers, undated (Box 14)
  - Inter-American Federation of Entertainment Workers, 1961-1962 (Box 14)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, 1986-1999, undated (Box 14)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Agreements, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Agreements, 2006 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1938-1952 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1962-1984 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 1 (Theatrical Protective Union) (New York, NY), 1892, 1937 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 1 (New York, NY), 1990-1995, undated (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 4 (Brooklyn, NY), 1981-1988 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 15, 1977 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 44, 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 52 (New York, NY), 1969-1993, undated (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 80 (Hollywood, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 165 (Sherman Oaks, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 306 (New York, NY), 1977-2005, undated (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 600 (Hollywood, CA), 1997-2003 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 600 (Hollywood, CA), 2004 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 644 (New York, NY), 1984, undated (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 683, 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 695 (Studio City, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 705 (Hollywood, CA), 1982-1985 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 706 (North Hollywood, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 717 (Los Angeles, CA), 1983 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 727, 1976 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 728 (Panorama City, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 729 (Hollywood, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 767, 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 771 (New York, NY), 1990, undated (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 790 (Hollywood, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 816, 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 839 (North Hollywood, CA), 1984 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 841, 1953 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 847 (Hollywood, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 854 (Hollywood, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 871 (Sherman Oaks, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local 876 (Hollywood, CA), 1982 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local B-751 (New York, NY), 1994 (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: Local H-63, undated (Box 15)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada: President's Report, 1944 (Box 15)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1971-1986, undated (Box 15)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers: Constitutions, 1936-1976 (Box 15)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers: Constitutions, 1981-2001 (Box 15)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers: Local 5 (Washington, DC), 1999 (Box 15)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers: Local 40 (New York, NY) and Local 341 (New York, NY), 1984-1985, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers: Local 46 (New York, NY), 2010 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers: Local 455 (New York, NY), 1960-1983, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers: Local 580 (New York, NY), 1960-1981 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Cleaning and Dye House Workers, 1938 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Factory Inspectors, 1896 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Factory Inspectors, 1887-1889 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Fire Fighters I, 1969-1989, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Fire Fighters II, 1969-1989, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Fire Fighters: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1938-1990 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Fire Fighters: Local 94 (Uniformed Firefighters Association of Greater New York), 1961-1969, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, 1942, 1977 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Labour Legislation, 1913 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Agreements and Contracts, 1919, 1946-1951 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Brochures, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Circular Letters, 1926-1959 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Constitutions, 1933-1961 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Conventions, 1936-1960 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: District Lodge 15 (New York, NY), 1903-1973, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Education Department, 1957-1959, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Ephemera, 1964, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Executive Council: Minutes, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Ladies' Auxiliary, 1933, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Leadership Schools, 1958-1963 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Local 751, 1940, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Local 1433, 1949, 1960 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Progressive Lodge 41 (St. Louis, MO), 1941 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Lodge 113 (Chicago, IL), 1961, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Lodge 402 (Manhattan and the Bronx, NY), 1948 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Aeronautical Lodge 747 (Burbank, CA), 1942 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Lodge 837 (St. Louis, MO), 1960 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Lodge 2120 (West Rock Lodge, New Haven, CT), 1960 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: New York State Council of Machinists, 1944-1962, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Newspaper Clippings and Articles on, 1900-1959 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Pamphlets and Publications, 1928-1954, undated (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Pamphlets and Publications, 1955-1963, c.1980 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Pension Plan and Health Insurance, 1955-1964 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Reports, 1931-1937 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Machinists: Rosters, 1936-1937 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Agreements & Contracts, 1989 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Brochures, 1976-1990, undated (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Circular Letters, 1984, 1990 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Constitutions, 1970-1989 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Eastern Air Lines Strike, 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Education Department, 1972, 1981, undated (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Fliers and Ephemera, 1993, undated (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Lodge 726 (San Diego, CA), 1979 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Local Lodge 946, 1968 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Local 2656 (New York, NY), 1990 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Pamphlets and Publications, 1968-1988, undated (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Press Releases, 1981, undated (Box 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Safety and Health, 1973, 1980 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Marble, Slate and Stone Polishers, Rubbers and Sawyers, Tile and Marble Setters Helpers and Marble Mosaic and Terrazzo Workers Helpers of the U.S. and Canada: By-laws, 1957 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Oil Field, Gas Well and Refinery Workers of America, 1934 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Sheet Metal Workers, 1983 (Box 17)
  - International Association of Siderographers, 1937 (Box 17)
  - International Broom and Whisk Makers' Union of America, 1925 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, 1892 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers and Helpers, 1919 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Iron Ship Builders' Protective and Benevolent Union of the United States and Canada, 1884 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers: Agreements, 1979, 1987 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1920-1981 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers: Local 802 (PA) I, undated (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers: Local 802 (PA) II, undated (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, 1957-1960 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Bookbinders: Constitutions, 1930-1963 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Bookbinders: Local 62 and 88 (Newark, NJ), 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Bookbinders: Local 119 (New York, NY), 1958, undated (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Agreements, 1960-1979 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Agreements, 1986-1992 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Clippings, Articles, 1965, 1981 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Constitutions, 1891, 1930-1969 (Box 17, Box 49, Folder 8, Box Shared Tamiment 186, Folder 11)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Constitutions, 1982-1986 (Box 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Conventions, 1929 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): History and Structure of, 1948, 1969-1976, 1991 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Labor Management Planning Committee, 1943 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 3: Agreements and Contracts, 1939, 1958-1978 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 3 (New York, NY): By-Laws, 1985, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 3 (New York, NY): Circular Letters, 1932, 1940, 1991, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 3 (New York, NY): Collective Bargaining, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: Local 3: Contracts, 1997-2001 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 3 (New York, NY): Education, 1940-1981, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 3 (New York, NY): Joint Industry Board, 1958-1989 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 3 (New York, NY): Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1957 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 3 (New York, NY): Pamphlets and Publications, 1932-1981, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 35, 1951 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 320, 1962 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 357 (Las Vegas, NV), 1967 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 394 (Auburn, NY), 1952 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 593, 1947 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 631 (Newburgh, NY), 1965 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 640, 1980 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 827, 1979 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 1049: Agreements, 1961-1962 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: Local 1049: Contract, 2001-2004 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 1130, 1956 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 1381, 1978 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 1419, 1960 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 1515, 1962 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 1741, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 1805 (Baltimore, MD), 1963 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Local 2321 (Middleton, MA), undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Newsletter Lifeline, Safety Trade Group 462, 1959-1960 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Only Righteous and Clean Living Electricians (ORACLE) (Chicago, IL), 1996-1999, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Pamphlets and Publications I, 1958-1996, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Pamphlets and Publications II, 1958-1996, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Stewart-Warner Corporation, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Zenith Electric Company, 1957, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1952-1966 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1976 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers: Local 56, 1933, 1967, undated (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Foundry Employees, 1919, 1937 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1976, 1996 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Maintenance-of-Way Employees, 1904 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Operative Potters, 1953 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades: Constitutions, 1975-1985 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades: Constitutions, 1990-1995 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades: Convention (26th General), 1989 (Box 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades: District Council 9 (New York, NY) I, 1965-2010 (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades: District Council 9 (New York, NY) II, 1965-2010 (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades: Insurance Fund, 1993 (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades: Legislative and Safety Conference, 1971 (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades: New York State Conference, 1969 (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades: Pamphlets and Publications, 1970, undated (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1939, 1943-1952 (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1939-1962, undated (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers: Local 107, undated (Box 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers: Local 213, 1971 (Box 19)